bharatbhasha.com 2017-12-19

# Privacy Policy for BharatBhasha.com

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by BharatBhasha.com (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers").

 **"Policy only for visitors"**   
We use 3rd party advertising agencies to display ads on our site including and not limited to - Google. These agencies use cookies to serve ads on our site. The cookies enable them and their partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our / other sites. These companies may use information collected from the cookie (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**"Personally Identifiable Information"**   
refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user)   
or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?**  
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers.

**What organizations are collecting the information?**  
In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such as credit card companies) who may provide such services as credit, insurance, and escrow services may collect this information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**  
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information. 

**With whom may the information may be shared?**  
Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Customers may be shared with other Authorized Customers who wish to evaluate potential transactions with other Authorized Customers. We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf. 

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by BharatBhasha.com is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of BharatBhasha.com except for use as indicated above. 

**What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed.

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?**  
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers.

**How does BharatBhasha.com use login information?**  
BharatBhasha.com uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.

**What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?**  
BharatBhasha.com has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors.  
Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility.   
Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information.   
Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers. 

**How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?**  
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Authorized Customers for any such occurrences. 

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**  
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure. 

**Links:**  
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
